What was it?
What's that?
A runaway?
I don't know. Cute.
I don't think that's ever happened to me before.
Oh, my God! There it is!
It was there, wasn't it?
Yes, I did.
I can't help it.
Eating cake and drinking alcohol makes me cry.
We were all geeks of some kind.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Everyone was weak.
Weak?
Everyone was weak. It was a mud fight.
Muddy game?
Yes, sir.
The kettle and the idol
Hello, I'm Kettle, the cute guy who grew up in Stardust.
I'd like to introduce today's guest.
This is our guest.
Hello, I'm Kurumi Hori, formerly known as Takoyaki Rainbow.
I'm Kurumi Hori, former member of Takoyaki Rainbow.
We have a guest from the Kansai region, Ms. Kurumi Hori.
Nice to meet you.
Ms. Kurumi Hori is now active in her hometown in Kansai.
She is a well-known reporter for ABC TV's "Ohayo Asahi Satsuday Desu" (Good Morning Saturday).
Thank you very much.
I am doing a lot of things here.
I'm sure you have visited many sightseeing spots in Kansai for your work.
Are there any places that stand out in your mind?
I go to Kansai as well, but I've also been on location outside of the prefecture quite a bit.
I think the most fun was in Hokkaido.
You've been to Hokkaido quite a bit, haven't you?
Hokkaido
Where did you go in Hokkaido?Where did you go in Hokkaido?
There's a hotel in Tomamu called Club Med.
I went there for an interview.
The buffet was so gorgeous!
I had another bowl of salmon roe three times!
Part of it was because I ate delicious food.
I also enjoyed the fact that I was able to go a little far away from home.
Hokkaido in the north?
Hokkaido in the north.
How far south?
I'm going to Okinawa next time.
That sounds great.
I'm sure it'll be on the air by now.
I met Hotta the other day.
It was in Yurakucho.
In the suburbs of Azuchi a year ago.
I think some of you may have seen him in the advertisements of Garden-no-Yu.
I also saw it the other day.
It was nighttime, but I took the train at Yurakucho.
At night?
This?
Yes, sir.
This is it.
It's a strange world, isn't it?
If someone can hold it, they can ride it.
That's what you're saying?
That's what I mean.
I was looking at an ad in front of Yurakucho.
There's a scene in the bathtub.
I thought, "Who's that? I was like...
What? He said it was a bird.
The guy who told me I was bobbing.
I said, "Isn't that a bird? I said...
Yes, it is.
I was pretty surprised.I was quite surprised.
Yes, I was, thank you.
We've been advertising for you.
Yes, it's been a long time.
I've been on it for quite a while.
Even now, people tell me via DM or Twitter
They tell me that they saw Hori's commercial.
We are often seen in front of Yurakucho.
Thank you very much.
Which one is in front of Yurakucho?
At night?
At night, in front of Yurakucho.
You'll be identified.
There's no Yurakucho-mae at night.
You don't get on?
I saw it when I got on.
Thank you very much.
Please watch it again, everyone.
If you haven't seen it yet, I think you really need to see it.
In addition, Hori is also active on the stage.
She will be performing at Tokyo Kinemaslab on September 6.
Tokyo Yakland VOL.3
Uguisu no Barajin" at Tokyo Kinemasurab on September 6.
Thank you very much.
How did you hear about this?
There's an event like this.
I'm sure I'll be singing at some of them.
But it's been a long time since I've performed in front of you all.
And it's been a long time since I've held one in Tokyo.
I had a birthday event in Osaka last winter.
I sang only a little at that time.
I think I'll sing a lot this time, so I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it!
Yes, I'm sure there will be quite a few performers.
I'm so happy to see so many people I haven't seen in a long time.
You don't get nervous?You don't get nervous?
Nervous...no.
I'm happy to see you for the first time in a long time, Yuzuki.
I'm sure we'll have a lot to talk about later.
I look forward to working with you today.
I've been doing this for about 450 hours.
That's amazing.
You've really gotten into it, haven't you?
This program is for Fukasawa-kun
Terami-san
Radical Gorilla-chan
Mr. Tatomi
Gutty-san provided the entertainment!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye!